Guide to the John P. Robin Papers, 1943-2000 AIS.1977.06
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Urban Redevelopment Authority, 1943-1994; IX.
  - Mayor Richard: Speeches, Grant Street, URA Real Estate Department, Clark Candy Company Committee, People Movers, URA Strategy 21; Bound reports regarding - Pittsburgh Technology and Industry Park: Preliminary Land Development Plan, Parkway East Industrial Park: A Proposal, Pittsburgh Technology Center: Final Land Development Plan, Market Square: First Draft, Civic Arena/Melody Tent Project, Pennsylvania Brighton: Redevelopment Proposal, Implementation Plan & Financial Proposal: Three Rives Corporate Center, Proposal: Three Rives Corporate Center, The Role of Downtown People Movers in Renaissance II; Presentation folder containing – Reshaping the Technological Landscape; Loose documents pertaining to – Professional correspondence, URA Memorandum, Newspaper articles, Detailed description of final Horizontal Elevator Study, Three Rivers Stadium Proposal, 1977-1992 (Box 64)
  - Carley Capital Group, Pirates; Bound reports regarding - An Evaluation of the North Side Revitalization Program, Request for Proposals: North Shore Place, Riverside Presentation Summary, Crawford Roberts: Request for Proposals, Housing Subsidy Programs, Home Improvement Loan Program: Status Report, Make Yourself at Home: On Pittsburgh's North Side, An Evaluation of The Rental Housing Improvement Program, The Vacant Property Review Committee: Report; Presentation folder containing – North Side Civic Development Council, Dravo Tower; Loose documents pertaining to – Professional correspondence, URA Memorandum, Newspaper articles, reports, Urban Development Law, 1977-1993 (Box 67)
  - Various documents concerning – Pittsburgh Convention Center, Washington's Landing; Bound reports regarding - Pennsylvania Railroad Terminal Building Study, Convention Center: Proposal and Redevelopment Area Plan, Market Study: Proposed Convention Center Hotel, Convention Center Redevelopment Area Plan & Proposal, David L. Lawrence Convention Center Expansion Study, Herr's Island Conference Center Study – Phase I, Herr's Island: Proposal for Redevelopment Activities, Redevelopment Area Plan, Allegheny County Marina Study, Washington's Landing Phase II Proposals, Washington's Land Promotional Material, Residential Analysis: Washington's Landing; Loose documents pertaining to – Professional correspondence, Newspaper articles, Washington's Landing, Penn Central Station, Herr's Landing, 1978-1991 (Box 68)
  - Hill District PAC, PA Economy League, Northside, Greyhound and Trailways; Bound reports regarding – Chinatown on the Allegheny, Shadyside Parking Facility Plan, Tasso Katselas Architect Planner; Presentation folders containing – Tour of URA Projects for 12th Floor, Motor Square Garden Fact Sheet, magazine articles; Loose documents pertaining to – URA memorandum, Professional correspondence, Shadyside Parking garage and Walnut Street Business District, Disposition Strategy for South Side Site, 1975-1993 (Box 71)
  - Minority Business Initiative, Women Owned Business Enterprise Directory, URA memorandum, Profession correspondence; Bound reports regarding – A Plan for Pittsburgh's Golden Triangle, Pittsburgh Wall Street District, Cities Reborn; Various magazines; Presentation folder containing – Andy Warhol Museum; Loose documents pertaining to – Minority/Women Business Enterprise reports, magazine articles, newspaper articles, 1962-1993 (Box 72)
  - Various meeting agendas and minutes; Bound reports regarding – Various redevelopment proposals; Loose documents pertaining to – URA meeting agendas, 1985-1994 (Box 73)
  - Various board meeting agendas and minutes, 1989-1991 (Box 74)
  - URA Mayor's Development Council –Agenda, minutes, and Professional correspondence; various documents concerning – Forks of the Ohio National Park, Oakland Portal, Schenley Park, Presidential Committee on the Library, Allegheny County on Community Development, Mon0Ohio Development and Reconstruction Commission; Bound reports regarding – Forks of the Ohio national park Alternatives Study, The Plan for the Pittsburgh Riverfront, Allegheny County Marina Study, The Headwaters District, Allegheny River Edge Park; Presentation folders containing – Schenley Park Centennial; Lose documents pertaining to – Professional correspondence, 1943-1992 (Box 77)
  - Schenley Plaza, Pittsburgh City Planning Commission meeting agenda and minutes, various documents concerning – Oakland Taskforce, Pittsburgh Cultural District Taskforce, and the Mayor's Taskforce; Bound reports regarding - The Economic Impact and Financial Health of the Arts in Pittsburgh, Pittsburgh Downtown Cultural District, The Firstside Cultural District Plan: A Strategy for Revitalization, The Plan for the Cultural District; Presentation folder containing – Three Rivers Stadium; Loose documents pertaining to – Professional correspondence, meeting minutes, 1975-1994 (Box 80)
- The World Bank, 1959-1973; X.
  This series contains documents pertaining to numerous countries such as Calcutta, Colombia, Iran, Singapore, Thailand, Turkey, Pakistan, Brazil, East Africa, and Jamaica. In addition there are several World Bank Annual Reports.
  - The Urbanization Problem in Less Developed Countries report, Urbanization: An Interim Policy Paper, Metropolitanization and National Policies for Growth, Speeches and papers by McNamara and others, Compound and Discounting Tables, Organization Chart,; Various documents concerning – Calcutta, Columbia, Iran, Singapore, Thailand, Turkey, Morocco, Jamaica, Nigeria, Kenya; Bound reports regarding – World Bank Annual Reports, The Indonesia Economy: Development Trends and Foreign Aid Requirements, Constraints Committee, Professional Correspondence, Report on Bombay, 1964-1973 (Box 10)
  - Course on Managing Urban Growth, Tourist maps; various documents concerning – Brazil (in Portuguese), 1967-1973 (Box 11)
  - Various documents concerning – French-Congo, Environmental Studies School (England), Bound reports regarding – British Aid Programme, IFHP Bulletin, Overseas Development Administration, Congo, Educational Workshop: Planning and Building for Development, Several in different languages, 1961-1971 (Box 12)
  - Various documents concerning – United Arab Republic, Egypt, Ethiopia, East Africa; Bound reports regarding – Ethiopia, 1959-1970 (Box 13-A)